Gerry Mulligan Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-148, 160)
  - Boo doo, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - Boplicity, Miles Davis
    - Parts (3 sets), score (nonet), Gil Evans arrangement; Parts: 1. Miles Davis and band; 2. Gunther Schuller transcription; 3. Condensed score, parts (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Parts (tentet), GM arrangement (Box-folder 112/1)
  - Bordado
    - Score (tentet), Incomplete (Box-folder 138/10)
    - Part (baritone saxophone), For the 1994 recording Paraiso (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Lead sheets, For the 1994 recording Paraiso (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Born to be blue, Mel Tormé
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Bossa nova tunes, Not written by GM
    - Lead sheets, Titles: Impressaos de Rio; Como sempre; untitled; Monsieu Binot; Brincadeirinha; O amor em paz; Cancion de amamercer; Chega de Suadade (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Brazil 1, Alternate title: Other side of the Sun
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Brazil stuff
    - Lead sheets; notes; lyrics, Laid in: correspondence regarding lyrics, arrangements; Titles: Theme for Jobim; Brazilia; Under a star; Paraiso; Other side of the sun; Love song to a tree; Willow tree (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Breadbox
    - Lead sheets; sketches, Note in GM's music library: New quartet, 6/24/94 (Box-folder 23A/1)
  - Brew's tune
    - Score, GM arrangement for Claude Thornhill, January 2, 1948 (Box-folder 146/5)
  - Bridgehampton South, Gary McFarland
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 46/2)
  - Bridgehampton strut, Gary McFarland
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 121/8)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 32/5)
  - Bright Angel Falls
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Box-folder 58/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Britney, Tom Boras
    - Part (piano, bass, baritone saxophone), On folder: Carriage House date, 3/14/89 (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Broadway
    - Score; sketch (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 145/9)
    - Score; parts (big band), GM arrangement for Claude Thornhill, Oct., 1948 (Box-folder 146/5)
    - Score; parts (octet), GM arrangement for Wynton Marsalis at Ravinia Festival, 1993 (Box-folder 131/6)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95, Broadway, Snowfall, Polka dots, Loverman (Box-folder 47/2)
    - Parts (big band), Incomplete; For CBS album (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Parts, Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 28/7)
  - Brother blues
    - Score; parts; sketches, For the 1995 recording Dragonfly; "Fortieth and Market" title is crossed out and replaced with "Brother blues" (Box-folder 68/5)
    - Score, Incomplete; For the 1995 recording Dragonfly (Box-folder 140/11)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Brotherhood of man
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Sketch (Concert Jazz Band), Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 43/5)
  - Brothers
    - Part (Box-folder 58/7)
  - Buddy Bolden
    - Photocopied transcribed solo part, Alvin Batiste transcription; Transcribed from trumpeter Bunk Johnson (whistling the solo from memory) (Box-folder 58/7)
  - Budo, Bud Powell
    - Score; parts (nonet) (Box-folder 129/8)
    - Parts (tentet) (Box-folder 111/5)
  - Bunny
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Buster's last stand
    - Conductor's score; parts (big band), Gil Evans arrangement; For Claude Thornhill Orchestra (Box-folder 60/1)
  - Butterfly with hiccups
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 123/4)
    - Sketch scores; parts (octet?), Arrangement for Dave Brubeck (Box-folder 50/2)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: GM tunes/lead sheets, returned by Dave Brubeck, May 1984 (Box-folder 82/2)
  - Bweebida bobbida
    - Score (sketch for 1st chorus) (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 122/1)
    - Score and parts (big band) (Box-folder 131/3)
    - Parts; lead sheet (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Parts (tenor, baritone saxophone), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Lead sheets; sketches, From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 19/1)
  - By your grace
    - Score (orchestra) (Box-folder 142/2)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 142/2)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, strings) (orchestra) (Box-folder 80/3)
  - Bye bye blackbird
    - Score (big band), Mark Lopeman arrangement (Box-folder 130/4)
  - C jam blues, Duke Ellington
    - Scores (Concert Jazz Band), Includes unused materials (Box-folder 129/5)
    - Score transcription; parts (big band), Gunther Schuller transcription (Box-folder 137/3)
  - Cabinteely blues
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Can't teach my old heart new tricks, Johnny Mercer/Richard A. Whiting
    - Score; lead sheet, Hubert Arnold arrangement; On folder: Margaret Whiting, arrangements; Laid in: letter from "Tex" to GM (Box-folder 137/5)
  - Capricious, Billy Taylor
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/3)
  - The cat walk
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Celebration, Harry Freedman
    - Score (orchestra), Gerry Mulligan's 50th birthday celebration (Box-folder 80/4)
    - Score; notes regarding score (orchestra), Gerry Mulligan's 50th birthday celebration (Box-folder 142/3)
    - Parts "cue" (orchestra), Gerry Mulligan's 50th birthday celebration (Box-folder 81/1)
    - Parts (percussion 2, bass) (orchestra), Gerry Mulligan's 50th birthday celebration (Box-folder 80/6)
    - Parts (saxophone solo) (orchestra), Gerry Mulligan's 50th birthday celebration (Box-folder 80/5)
  - Centering
    - Score (orchestra), Earle Brown arrangement; Inscribed from Brown to GM (Box-folder 90/1)
  - Chalk gardens
    - Lead sheets; sketches (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Changes, Dec 3, '92 untitled
    - Lead sheets; song lists (quartet), On folder: New songs for quartet 2-9-93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - The chant, Jelly Roll Morton
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Mel Stitzel arrangement (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Score (horn trio), Mel Stitzel arrangement (Box-folder 67/12)
    - Parts (clarinet, piano, bass), GM personal performance parts (Box-folder 116)
  - Chasin' the Bird
    - Lead sheets (quintet), Incomplete; For quintet recording with Gerry Niewood; Laid in: notes on "Tape marked GM 5," tune lists with timings and notes (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Chega de Saudade, Antonio Carlos Jobim
    - Lead sheets, For the 1994 recording Paraiso (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/12)
  - Chelsea Bridge, Billy Strayhorn
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 20/17)
  - Cherry pickens
    - Part (unidentified), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Lead sheets, Yale Jazz Festival, 1988; On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Chicago concerto, Richard Peaslee; Other title: Concerto '67
    - Parts (extra baritone saxophone) (orchestra) (Box-folder 81/6)
  - Chick came around, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - Christmas music, Traditional
    - Printed lead sheets (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Chronicles
    - Parts (extra baritone saxophone) (orchestra) (Box-folder 80/2)
  - Chuggin'
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 145/11)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 33/3)
  - Circadian dysrhythmia
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Clarinet exercises by Gerry Mulligan
    - Lead sheets; sketches - exercises, Laid in: notes (Box-folder 22/14)
  - Close as pages in a book, Sigmund Romberg
    - Lead sheets, From "Synclavier" folders (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Come in from the rain, Melissa Manchester/Carol Bayer Sager
    - Part (tenor saxophone) (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Lead sheets, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Come out, come out where ever you are, Sammy Cahn/Jule Styne
    - Part (bass) (Box-folder 20/19)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Come rain or come shine, Harold Arlen/Johnny Mercer
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Transcription of Gerry Mulligan solo, Transcribed by Rich Daniels (Box-folder 23/11)
  - Come with me
    - Lead sheet (quintet), For quintet recording with Gerry Niewood; Laid in: notes on "Tape marked GM 5," tune lists with timings and notes (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Complicity, Jimmy Owens
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Com Alma, Dizzy Gillespie
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Concerto for saxophone and orchestra, Frank Proto
    - Score, Laid in: clipping; notes regarding score (Box-folder 142/1)
    - Solo parts; exercises (orchestra) (Box-folder 80/1)
  - Cool fortune
    - Lead sheets; sketch; part (baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Lead sheet; trumpet score (Box-folder 23A/1)
  - Counterpoise #2, John Carisi
    - Part (baritone saxophone), On folder: Wilder winds concert, baritone saxophone solo parts (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Country beaver
    - Parts (Box-folder 9/38)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Crazy day
    - Parts; sketches (Box-folder 58/9)
  - Crescendo in blue, Duke Ellington
    - Transcription of Paul Gonsalves saxophone solo, Newport Jazz Festival, 1956 (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Curtain call
    - Lead sheets; song lists (quartet), On folder: New songs for quartet 2-9-93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Curtains
    - Sketch scores (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 127/2)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Parts; sketches (sextet) (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Dalvatore Sally, George Handy
    - Parts; conductor's score (big band), George Handy arrangement for Boyd Raeburn Orchestra (Box-folder 60/3)
  - Damn the torpedos
    - Lead sheets; part (baritone saxophone), On folder: Carriage House date, 3/15/89 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Parts (bass part only), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Dance of the truck, From the 1977 film La menace
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 810/6)
  - A dance on the Earth, Harry Freedman
    - Score (orchestra) (Box-folder 144/8)
  - Dancing all day Sunday
    - Score (big band) (Box-folder 133/15)
    - Parts; sketches (big band), Title "Country beaver" on folder is crossed out (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Sketch, Title on manuscript: "Hercules"; Note in GM's music library: "Dancing all day Sunday" (Box-folder 52/6)
  - Dancing in the dark
    - Score (big band), On title page: January, '52; On folder: For Kenton (Box-folder 133/6)
  - Dancing shoes
    - Score (big band) (Box-folder 131/12)
  - Dangerously, Lyrics by Marty Brill
    - Lead sheets; lyrics (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Danielle, Al Cohn
    - Lead sheet, Laid in: letter from Al Cohn to GM about Danielle, 1980 February 26 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Darn that dream, Jimmy Van Heusen
    - Score; sketches (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 122/2)
    - Score (nonet), GM arrangement (Box-folder 137/8)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Parts (nonet), GM arrangement (Box-folder 137/8)
    - Part (tenor saxophone) (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Parts (tentet) (Box-folder 111/7)
    - Part (trumpet) (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Parts (baritone, trumpet, trombone, bass?), From "Standards" folder; On verso: "Walkin' shoes"; "Soft shoe"; "Bernie's tune"; Darn that dream"; "Motel" (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Parts (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 160/1)
    - Sketches, On folder: Misc. works, some for Count Basie Band (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Davenport blues, Bix Beiderbeck
    - Parts; lead sheets, Note in GM's music library: Music from record dates (Box-folder 53/6)
  - Dave's 1st piece, Dave Grusin?
    - Piano part (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Dead end
    - Lead sheet, From Kai Winding folder (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Dearly beloved, Jerome Kern
    - Parts (Box-folder 56/9)
  - Deathtrap, Johnny Mandel
    - Score (Box-folder 117/7)
  - Deception, Miles Davis
    - Scores; chord charts (nonet), Laid in: correspondence; For the 1991 recording Re-birth of the cool (Box-folder 137/7)
    - Parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 111/6)
  - Decidedly
    - Score (big band), On title page: Jan. '52; On folder: For Kenton (Box-folder 133/9)
    - Sketch score, On folder: For Stan Kenton Orch. (eventually turned into chart of "Walkin") (Box-folder 145/15)
  - Deep in a dream
    - Part (baritone saxophone) (orchestra), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Deep river
    - Part (baritone saxophone) (orchestra), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Demanton, Jon Eardley
    - Score (sextet), On folder: Sextet - 4 horn score by Jon Eardley (Box-folder 140/3)
    - Parts (sextet) (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Lead sheets; sketches, From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Dial M for Music
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Diamond Jim
    - Sketches (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Disc jockey jump
    - Score (octet), On folder: "Songbook" album, sax section scores by Bill Holman (Box-folder 135/7)
    - Parts, On folder: Saxes arr. "Mulligan Songbook" album (originals) (Box-folder 56/5)
  - Do you know what I see?
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Lead sheets, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Sketches; notes on lyrics (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Dolphin dance
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Don't be late
    - Lead sheets, From Kai Winding folder (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Don't get around much anymore, Duke Ellington
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 126/3)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part; Includes "C jam" insert (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Includes "C jam" insert (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Don't tell mama, Other title: Don't tell Basie
    - Lead sheets (quintet), Laid in: notes on "Tape marked GM 5," tune lists with timings and notes (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Don't worry, Gale Madden
    - Lead sheets; lyrics (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Dragonfly
    - Score; parts, For the 1995 recording Dragonfly; "Listening to Astor" title is crossed out and replaced with "Dragonfly" (Box-folder 68/4)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Dream girl
    - Lyric sheets (Box-folder 15/1)
  - The Duke
    - Part (baritone saxophone) (orchestra), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Duke medley
    - Parts (trumpet, tenor saxophone), From "Standards" folder; Sketches of "Soft shoe" and "Bernie's tune"; On verso: "Darn that dream" and "Motel" (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Dziekuye - thank you
    - Part (baritone saxophone) (orchestra), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Easy if you know how to do it
    - Lead sheet, From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Easy living, Leo Robin / Ralph Rainger
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 124/6)
    - Parts (quartet), On folder: For P. Desmond quartet (Box-folder 53/4)
    - Lead sheets, Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Eight bar blues
    - Lead sheets; sketches, On folder: New quartet, 6/24/94 (Box-folder 23A/1)
  - E-lag
    - Part (trumpet), Title on folder: Small band trumpet parts (Box-folder 66/2)
  - Elementals, Dave Brubeck
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, alto saxophone) (Box-folder 81/8)
  - Elevation
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, tenor saxophone, trumpet, trombone) (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Lead sheets, From "Kai Winding" folder (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Ellington medley: Moon mist; Sentimental mood, Duke Ellington
    - Parts; sketches (sextet) (Box-folder 140/1)
  - Embarcadero, Paul Desmond
    - Lead sheet with lyrics (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Empty ballroom blues
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), John Murtaugh arrangement (Box-folder 44/2)
  - Engine #9
    - Parts, Incomplete (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Entente for baritone saxophone and orchestra
    - Parts (strings) (orchestra) (Box-folder 88/1)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 100/2)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 100/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: 1st set, woodwinds, brass, perc. (Box-folder 97/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: 1st set, string parts (Box-folder 98/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: String parts (Box-folder 96/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Woodwinds, brass, perc. (Box-folder 95/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Strings, perc, horns, harp; used in Washington - oldest parts with intro removed (Box-folder 99/1)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 80/2)
  - Erudition, Bob Brookmeyer
    - Part (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Lead sheet, Bob Brookmeyer arrangement; Titles: Simple life; Erudition; Open country; Just in time; Who could care; Love jumped out; So nice (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Etude: "Quiet song" for small orchestra
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), First eight bars only (Box-folder 118/3)
  - Etude for Franca
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets, On folder: Carriage House Date 3/14/89 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/11)
  - Etude No. 3
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 28/1)
  - Etudes for saxophone, John Russo
    - Lead sheets, Laid in: letter from J. Russo to GM (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Every good boy does fine
    - Lead sheet, For James Moody (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Everything happens to me, Tom Adair / Matt Dennis
    - Sketch, Last 8 bars of the out chorus; Laid in: "Zoot" sketches (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Sketch, From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Everything I've got, Richard Rodgers
    - Lead sheets, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Evie, Barry Manilow
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/4)
  - The eyes have it, D. Johnson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/19)
  - Face lift
    - Lead sheet, Yale Jazz Festival, 1988; On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Fair weather, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Fall out
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Feelin' good, Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good
    - Score (strings) (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Parts (strings) (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Parts (Piano, guitar, bass) (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Parts (strings) (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Parts (rhythm section) (Box-folder 61/2)
  - Fertile lands: Enrico Intra, Nuova Civilta
    - Lead sheets; parts (baritone saxophone), Note in GM's music library: Gerry Mulligan meets Enrico Intra, 1976 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Festive minor
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 125/1)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (extra baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet; parts (bass, drums), On folder: Art Farmer, Lincoln Center '94, The art of trumpet (Box-folder 24/1)
  - The final programme - Jerry Cornelius Theme, Paul Beaver
    - Parts (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Finale
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Note: For Brendan Behan, Olatunji, Carmen De Lavallade show (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Five brothers
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95, Five brothers, Robin's nest, La Paloma, TNT" (Box-folder 47/3)
    - Part (trumpet) (quartet), On folder: quartet trumpet parts - originals (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Parts (sextet outchorus), Tenor saxophone part is missing (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Part (tenor sax "Zoot"), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Lead sheets; sketches; parts (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Lead sheets; sketch for brass, Note in GM's music library: Misc. parts (Box-folder 65/5)
  - Five Spot after dark, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Flash, Other title: Swinger
    - Parts (horn, bass), Note: "Swinger" crossed out on bass part, "Flash" added as title (Box-folder 66/5)
  - Flying
    - Piano part, lead sheet (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Lead sheets, At top of one lead sheet, "Italiano" is crossed out and retitled "Venezuela" (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
  - The flying Scotsman
    - Score; parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 113/5)
    - Score (tentet), Inscribed: orignial score, tentet arr., reductions (Box-folder 129/3)
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 129/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 45/2)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, drums), GM personal performance parts (Box-folder 116)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Focus
    - Parts (solo saxophone), On folder: Solo sax parts from Marin Alsop; Inscribed note: The Sauter pieces we were interested in are: #6, #5, #4, #1 (Box-folder 62/1)
  - A foggy day
    - Sketch score(big band) (Box-folder 140/5)
  - Folk song
    - Lead sheet, On folder: new songs for quartet 2-9-93 (Box-folder 23/12)
  - For an unfinished woman
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Inscribed: revised score 2/26/86 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Inscribed: old parts (Box-folder 128/5)
    - Sketch score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Score; parts (Brubeck groups), On folder: for combined Brubeck groups, Deshon original parts, sketch score (Box-folder 139/5)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Inscribed: old parts (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Parts (extra baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - For God's sake, Elizabeth
    - Part (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Forgetful, George Handy
    - Parts, George Handy arrangement for Boyd Raeburn Orchestra (Box-folder 60/4)
  - Forlorn, Ross Schneider
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Forty days